Many of you had asked in the comments that
how much commission is received by ICICI BCD and
in how many days does the commission come, all these
questions were asked by you people in the comments, so
I was
asked to make a video about it, so in today's
video I am going to tell you all that, how much
commission do you get in ICICI
and how much commission does one get,
we will talk about all these topics in today's video, so
hello friends, I am Rahul and I
welcome you all very much today
on Rest Technical Guruji channel, today's
video is going to be very important, do
not miss any point of the video,
turn on the saver mode for every point and along with this,
if you have come to the channel for the first time, then do
subscribe and like the video
and I would like to make a request to you that you should watch the
video completely, talk to your friends
that the retention of the video should be good and
every video should reach all of you and do
not forget to share the video with your friends
and many new videos have also come on this channel, so do
not forget about them, let us talk about them
Regarding ICICI Bank CSP commission, okay, there is
a commission structure given here,
here you get a commission of 0.40 on up to ₹100, which
means that once
you have cleared here, there is a share of BC, it
also stops the point, okay, that is, the
commission is structured,
you do not get more than 404 points commission,
okay in ICICI BSE, suppose
if you have withdrawn ₹1000, then
you get 0.40 percent, whatever amount you
withdraw, you get only 0.40 percent,
okay, so
add a big snake, whatever
amount you deposit, you will get 140 percent
commission on it and after this, those who have
given the maximum typing that they will
not give you Rs.11 or 25 paise more, okay,
their deduction is that if you complete any transaction up to
Rs.10000, then they will
give you only 0.40 percent and  Out of that also, whatever you get for Rs. 9, they will
not give much money, so how do you feel
about ICICI, please comment about it,
what is the commission structure, can't they do better than the commission on S letter
degree
because it is giving the best commission on earth
today, so this is the commission
structure and here you can withdraw Rs.
1000, if you plus it, zero point six
0.40, then
here you will get a commission of Rs. 4,
₹1000, okay,
so this is the net share of Net BC, let's say Rs.
4, okay, similarly, on Rs. 3000, you earn Rs. 3000,
but you will be
given Rs. 9 here, and on that you earn Rs. 9, so
here you earn Rs.
3000, see here it is written here that, see, on Rs. 3000, you get Rs. 11 commission, which is
in CSC, you
get Rs. 11 commission, on withdrawing Rs. 3000, here the
commission is less, CSC Digipay  So
you should take a good look at this commission structure,
you can also take a screenshot of it
and now the question arises that
in how many days does your commission come because
Delhi is not updated, this commission
comes to the account and in how many
days does it come, the question arises, so for this
I take you to my ICICI
net banking because I have kept it logged in,
here I had done a lot of
transactions in the environment and
I have not done any traction
from ICI, so before this the
commission, the commission of the transactions that I had done in April and
March, came
here on 18th May 2021, the commission of the
tractions that I had done before this came on 18th May
2021, see this, it is
written here CMS CSC one Vansh service
and ₹70
posted here and I had set a lot of time
between the month of March and April, that is
in the month of March and April, whatever commission there is, the
commission of all the tractions that were done, came here in the area of ​​Rs.  And
this May minister has come for the first time
on 18th May, so it seems that this AC has
deposited the commission for the first time on 18th May
and similarly the commission will come in the group of young men
in the account of the century, but here
this is the first time in 3 months that our commission has
come on 18th May, area rupees, so you
can understand that from here you will get
commission on monthly basis, so we hope all your
doubts are cleared
regarding ICBC commission,
so we will meet you again with a new video and on
which topic do you want the next video, do
comment and if you liked the video then
like and share it with your friends.